This billionaire just made the biggest move
that's going to change the crypto space forever.
So much so that a bunch of new
startups are going to form because of this move.
The main reason I'm pointing out Mark Andreessen
to you today is because of his amazing track
record as an investor and entrepreneur. He
co-founded Netscape and owns one of the biggest
Silicon Valley venture capital firms. As an
investor, his track record is amazing. He's
one of the biggest holders in Facebook, Pinterest,
GitHub, Twitter, and acquired a majority stake in
Skype before it was acquired by Microsoft. But
what makes this guy the father of crypto?
Well, some of the biggest crypto companies out
there today, he holds major investments in. He
was one of the original investors into Coinbase,
which is an online trading platform where people
can buy and trade cryptocurrencies. He was
also one of the main investors into OpenSea,
which is the NFT marketplace where
people are buying and trading digital assets.
He's a huge proponent of Bitcoin. In fact,
he's invested in a lot of Bitcoin-ran startups.
If you're trying to follow along in the crypto
space and need somebody to follow that has a
track record, then make sure you check
out his website. He's a great investor.
It's probably Marc Andreessen. Well, what is this
big move that Marc Andreessen made that's got the
crypto space buzzing right now that it's about
to change forever? And many startups that are
going to come from this idea that I'm going
to bring up later in this video. Marc Andreessen
and his team are in contact with an NFT
project called Bored Ape Yacht Club. If you've seen images
going around the internet of crazy looking monkeys
that are selling on the internet for $200,000,
then you probably know a little bit of what
I'm talking about. Why on earth would a billionaire,
someone who's had such a great track record
in the crypto space and the tech space,
be so interested to pour billions
of dollars into a project centered around
pictures of crazy looking monkeys? So if you've
been following along in the crypto space enough
to know what NFTs are and how they work, then
you're going to understand a lot of what I am
about to say. But if you don't, to put it
quite simple, Bored Ape Yacht Club is an NFT project.
And basically, they specialize in the concept
of exclusivity. People are paying hundreds of
thousands of dollars for this image of a monkey
that looks crazy. Each one is unique and individual
and one of the 10,000 that were made. And they
want to be part of this exclusive club that only
the rich, the famous, and those can afford a
Bored Ape can become a part of this mastermind.
What's going to happen is probably Marc Andreessen
is pouring money into this project because they
want to take the owners of the Bored Ape
Yacht Club project, want to take this and do things
with it, build a mastermind, go on yacht
trips, clubs, financial groups, things of that nature,
and only the rich and famous can get
in. That's what makes it so crazy and special.
But how is this being done with
pictures of monkeys? Well, basically, an NFT,
if you don't know, is a digital asset
that's bought and sold on a blockchain where people
can verify that you're the digital owner of that
asset. It's not like you can just right click and
save a JPEG image of the crazy monkey and say,
oh, I own a Bored Ape Yacht Club. People can easily
just go to the blockchain on OpenSea, one
of Marc Andreessen's investments, and verify that you're
the holder of that digital asset that's worth
$200,000 to millions of dollars. So to bring it
back to this, how does Marc Andreessen, a
billionaire, pouring $4 to $5 billion into this
NFT project? And what does this mean for
the crypto space? Essentially, the way things that
have always been done with NFTs is that people buy
an NFT to invest in a project and hope that
that digital asset increases in value or them
holding that asset can give them access to
exclusive digital and physical benefits, such
as attending events, maybe getting free merch,
or holding an NFT of a music artist and you
buy their NFT of a song. You're hoping that you get
you know, merch from that artist or
you get extra bonus content and free music,
things of that nature. So Marc selecting the Bored
Ape Yacht Club as to be this major billion dollar
investment is very interesting because of all
the celebrities that have already bought into it,
such as Lil Baby, Kevin Hart, Snoop Dogg, Gwyneth
Paltrow, a bunch of people from all across the
globe that are rich and famous are buying into
this project. What Bored Ape Yacht Club can do
with an investment like Marc Andreessen is they
can take this and do yacht masterminds. They can
open up their own clubs that offer exclusive
offers and entrance to their holders. And obviously, if
you're rich or you're not famous enough to buy one
of these Bored Ape Yacht Clubs, then you can't get
in. You don't get the exclusive benefits of
the mastermind. So how is this changing the crypto
space? Well, essentially, if you want to invest in an
NFT project, all you have to do is buy the
NFT on a marketplace such as OpenSea. Now,
Marc Andreessen and his venture capital firm are
opening up Pandora's box by basically saying you can
invest in the NFT project by buying an NFT.
But what if you just directly invest into the
NFT project as a company, like you're buying stock in
a private equity firm? Or buying a private
equity company? Well, that's a different story. You can
buy crypto in the NFT project, but you can
also invest in crypto in a private equity company. So
if you want to invest in crypto, you can invest
in crypto in a private equity company. This is huge
for the crypto space because now not only can I
buy and sell digital coins, I can buy and sell
NFTs, but I can also invest my money into
a physical project. If I believe in the founders
and what they're trying to do with the project, I
don't even have to buy just the NFT. I can invest
in the company itself. This is going to spark
a lot of billion dollar startup ideas where basically
tons of crypto investors can choose whether they want to
be a holder of the NFT or if they just
want to invest and increase their digital, their digital
assets. And I think this is going to be
a very powerful opportunity. So if you're looking to
invest in crypto, you can invest in crypto. So
I'm not going to talk about the digital value
of their asset. They don't really care about the
physical or digital value that the asset's going to
bring them for holding it. They just want the
return on the investment. They're going to be
able to now invest into the physical NFT project.
Essentially, a startup idea could come out where
you basically are trading coins on one tab. You're
trading NFTs on the other, but you're
also, you're choosing between different NFT projects
that you want to pour money into. For
example, whenever the startup comes out to where they're
going to turn to hotel keys in the NFTs,
where it's going to require that, you know, that the
other person is going to be the one that's going to
be the one that's going to be the one that's going
to get a private key and turn it into
a multipurpose playlist and being able to sell it
to how they're because when they got a
regular investment for the library or their software or
their products, that's when the narrative used to
be sort of beefed up a little bit, right?
So they were swamped in there. So out of
theше Chop-a- filters is where you're going to want to
focused on. So one of you should another
investing in crypto projects ideas. Given the kind of
cuando yo hago una entrevista que puedo
seguir conteniendo de поти, feeling well informed and
you're looking into a separate asset, ultimately harder for
your сам Воon. That may be it. I homes
to use for hotels to use for their guests that
have to come and check in if it's one thing. we've
investments outside of just buying the physical nft then
it might be wise to stock up on some of
those nfts as well but yeah it'll be interesting
to see what mark andreason does over the next
course of the year or other big crypto players
comment what you guys think of this move and how
it's going to change the crypto space and if any
of you guys are holding nfts right now would like
to know what they are yeah if you're out there
and you're looking for the next big startup idea well
looks like i just gave you one so thanks
for watching the video hope you like the content
make sure to subscribe for more content
like this and we'll see you soon